{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Metal Ceiling Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40438/":{"taskOID":40438,"originalTaskOID":40438,"setID":729,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5178,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5312,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Residential","answerDisplayText":"Residential","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1507,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Commercial","answerDisplayText":"Commercial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5324,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Restoration","answerDisplayText":"Restoration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5179,"questionDisplayText":"Style of Metal Ceiling","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What style of metal ceiling do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6468,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional/Classic","answerDisplayText":"Traditional/Classic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":862,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Asian","answerDisplayText":"Asian","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":844,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Art Deco","answerDisplayText":"Art Deco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1306,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Celled","answerDisplayText":"Celled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1611,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Contemporary","answerDisplayText":"Contemporary","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5181,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Metal Desired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of metal do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6380,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Tin (must be finished with oil-based paint)","answerDisplayText":"Tin (must be finished with oil-based paint)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5053,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready-to-paint aluminum or steel","answerDisplayText":"Ready-to-paint aluminum or steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4840,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Powder coated white","answerDisplayText":"Powder coated white","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4839,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Powder coated custom color","answerDisplayText":"Powder coated custom color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1117,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bright aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Bright aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1119,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bright stainless steel","answerDisplayText":"Bright stainless steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5491,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Satin stainless steel","answerDisplayText":"Satin stainless steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1634,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Copper","answerDisplayText":"Copper","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1390,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Chrome","answerDisplayText":"Chrome","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1098,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Brass","answerDisplayText":"Brass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1141,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Bronze","answerDisplayText":"Bronze","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5178,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5312,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Residential","answerDisplayText":"Residential","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1507,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Commercial","answerDisplayText":"Commercial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5324,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Restoration","answerDisplayText":"Restoration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5312,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Residential","answerDisplayText":"Residential","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1507,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Commercial","answerDisplayText":"Commercial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5324,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Restoration","answerDisplayText":"Restoration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5179,"questionDisplayText":"Style of Metal Ceiling","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What style of metal ceiling do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6468,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional/Classic","answerDisplayText":"Traditional/Classic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":862,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Asian","answerDisplayText":"Asian","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":844,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Art Deco","answerDisplayText":"Art Deco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1306,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Celled","answerDisplayText":"Celled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1611,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Contemporary","answerDisplayText":"Contemporary","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6468,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional/Classic","answerDisplayText":"Traditional/Classic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":862,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Asian","answerDisplayText":"Asian","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":844,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Art Deco","answerDisplayText":"Art Deco","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1306,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Celled","answerDisplayText":"Celled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1611,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Contemporary","answerDisplayText":"Contemporary","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5181,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Metal Desired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of metal do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6380,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Tin (must be finished with oil-based paint)","answerDisplayText":"Tin (must be finished with oil-based paint)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5053,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready-to-paint aluminum or steel","answerDisplayText":"Ready-to-paint aluminum or steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4840,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Powder coated white","answerDisplayText":"Powder coated white","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4839,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Powder coated custom color","answerDisplayText":"Powder coated custom color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1117,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bright aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Bright aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1119,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bright stainless steel","answerDisplayText":"Bright stainless steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5491,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Satin stainless steel","answerDisplayText":"Satin stainless steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1634,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Copper","answerDisplayText":"Copper","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1390,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Chrome","answerDisplayText":"Chrome","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1098,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Brass","answerDisplayText":"Brass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1141,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Bronze","answerDisplayText":"Bronze","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6380,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Tin (must be finished with oil-based paint)","answerDisplayText":"Tin (must be finished with oil-based paint)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5053,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready-to-paint aluminum or steel","answerDisplayText":"Ready-to-paint aluminum or steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4840,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Powder coated white","answerDisplayText":"Powder coated white","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4839,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Powder coated custom color","answerDisplayText":"Powder coated custom color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1117,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bright aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Bright aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1119,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bright stainless steel","answerDisplayText":"Bright stainless steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5491,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Satin stainless steel","answerDisplayText":"Satin stainless steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1634,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Copper","answerDisplayText":"Copper","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1390,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Chrome","answerDisplayText":"Chrome","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1098,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Brass","answerDisplayText":"Brass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1141,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Bronze","answerDisplayText":"Bronze","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40438/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40438,"taskName":"Metal Ceiling Covers - Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Repair or Install Ceiling Covers","xmTaskDescriptor":"Metal Ceiling Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":40,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Carpenters carpentry tiles structural rough","textMessagingName":"Metal Ceiling Cover","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes tin plate, simulated tin plate \u0026 other ceiling treatments that are used to cover \u0026 decorate ceilings.","rolloverShortDesc":"Decorative panels applied to the ceiling surface.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Install Ceiling Covers.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Metal Ceiling Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Metal Ceiling Tiles, Covers, etc.","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":9,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Metal Ceiling Cover install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Metal Ceiling Covers - Install or Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Metal Ceiling Project","urlName":"Metal-Ceiling-Covers-Install-or-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Metal Ceiling Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Carpenters,carpentry,tiles,structural,rough,tin,ceilings,leak,Covers,Metal,Ceiling","emcCategoryOid":-12010,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":729,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}